wetu.com 2011-11-10

# wetu - Privacy Policy

_**Purpose**_

This policy sets out the manner in which WETU handles personal information submitted by or collected from you whilst visiting the WETU site.

This Privacy Policy forms part of the Terms and Conditions of Use of this website. Continued use of this website means that you agree to the provisions of this Policy and are bound by them.

_**Collection of personal data**_

WETU collects only what is necessary and we will use it only for the purpose for which it is required.

_**Protection of information**_

WETU will neither sell your personal information to anyone nor otherwise dispose of it to a third party otherwise than as set out in the Policy. We will not attempt to obtain your permission to do so by deceptive means 

WETU will not disclose your personal information unless acting under a good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (i) conform to legal requirements or comply with legal process; or (ii) to act to protect the interests of its members or others.

If we do not require it any longer, we will delete any personal information held

We neither store nor retain any credit card information 

Personal information collected by WETU is stored secure operating environments that are not available to the public.

_**Collection of anonymous data**_

In order to provide the best and most relevant service, we may use technology to collect information about the use of the site . This technology is not able to identify individual users but simply allows the website to collect statistics.

In order to do this we use cookies. A cookie is a small file that is placed on your hard drive in order to keep your interaction with this website and will log:

  * The Internet Protocol (IP) address from which you access our website. An IP address is the unique number that is automatically assigned to the computer that you are using whenever you are surfing the web.
  * The type of browser (such as Internet Explorer or Mozilla) and operating system (such as Windows Vista or MacOS) used to access our site
  * The date and time when the website is accessed, for the purpose of traffic and statistical monitoring.
  * The pages visited, for the purpose of improving the usefulness of our website by providing helpful links and removing pages that are not read.

If you do not wish Cookies to be employed it is possible to alter the manner in which your browser handles Cookies. Please note that, if this is done, certain services on this web site may not be available

Wetu will not send you any unsolicited information, including e mail, regarding any third party commercial offers or advertisements, unless your prior consent has been received.

**_Contacting us_**

If you have any questions concerning the privacy policies of WETU which are not covered in this statement, please contact us with your questions.

This site may contain links to other Web sites and is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of these Web sites. Furthermore this site uses third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit the site.
